Official Exterminator 2: Heaven's Hell is a action
film directed by Phillip Ko Fai.
Phil (Mark Watson) wants to bring down Lucas (Mike Abbott) as he made
his brother lose all his money in a financial scam.
Enlisting the help from Alfred, a Taiwanese thug, that goes
about getting even in a most violent manner.
Hong Kong cut and paste edit of the 1983 Taiwanese Film "討海的人
" (The Fishing Adventure) with new scenes.
Treblinka (Polish: [trɛˈbliŋ.ka]; German: [tʁeˈblɪŋka]) was the second-deadliest extermination camp to be built
and operated by Nazi Germany in occupied Poland during World War II, second only to Auschwitz.
It was in a forest north-east of Warsaw, four kilometres (2+1⁄2 miles) south of
the village of Treblinka in what is now the Masovian Voivodeship.
The camp operated between 23 July 1942 and 19 October 1943 as part of
Operation Reinhard, the deadliest phase of the Final Solution.
During this time, it is estimated that between 800,000 and 925,000 Jews were
murdered in its gas chambers, along with 2,000 Romani people.
More Jews were murdered at Treblinka than at any other Nazi
extermination camp apart from Auschwitz-Birkenau.
Managed by the German SS with assistance from Trawniki guards – recruited from among Soviet
POWs to serve with the Germans – the camp consisted of two separate units.
Treblinka I was a forced-labour camp (Arbeitslager) whose prisoners worked in the gravel pit or
irrigation area and in the forest, where they cut wood to fuel the cremation pits.
Between 1941 and 1944, more than half of its 20,000 inmates were
murdered via shootings, hunger, disease and mistreatment.
The second camp, Treblinka II, was an extermination camp (Vernichtungslager), referred
to euphemistically as the SS-Sonderkommando Treblinka by the Nazis.
A small number of Jewish men who were not murdered immediately upon arrival became members of its
Sonderkommando whose jobs included being forced to bury the victims' bodies in mass graves.
These bodies were exhumed in 1943 and cremated on large
open-air pyres along with the bodies of new victims.
Gassing operations at Treblinka II ended in October 1943
following a revolt by the prisoners in early August.
Several Trawniki guards  were killed and 200 prisoners  escaped from the
camp; almost a hundred survived the subsequent pursuit.
The camp was dismantled in late 1943.
A farmhouse for a watchman was built on the site and the ground
ploughed over in an attempt to hide the evidence of genocide.
In the postwar Polish People's Republic, the government bought most of the land where the
camp had stood, and built a large stone memorial there between 1959 and 1962.
In 1964, Treblinka was declared a national monument of Jewish martyrdom
in a ceremony at the site of the former gas chambers.
In the same year, the first German trials were held regarding the
crimes committed at Treblinka by former SS members.
After the end of communism in Poland in 1989, the number of
visitors coming to Treblinka from abroad increased.
An exhibition centre at the camp opened in 2006.
It was later expanded and made into a branch of the Siedlce Regional Museum.
The tone is dark.